Happy New Year, Jay.
سنة جديدة سعيدة يا جاي.
I feel like I’m going crazy.
أشعر وكأنني سأصاب بالجنون.
Or am I already crazy?
أم أنني مجنون بالفعل؟
So much has happened ever since I wore this uniform.
لقد حدث الكثير منذ ذلك الحين ارتديت هذا الزي الرسمي.
Section E!!!
القسم ه !!!
Why did you even do that, Jay-jay?
لماذا فعلت ذلك حتى، جاي جاي؟
You almost got carried away!
لقد كدت أن تبتعد!
You really are crazy!
أنت حقا مجنون!
You’re weak!
أنت ضعيف!
Later I’m going to see the King of Assholes,
في وقت لاحق سأفعل شاهد ملك المتسكعون،
and after that…
وبعد ذلك…
I already accepted Yuri’s proposal,
لقد قبلت بالفعل اقتراح يوري،
so I shouldn’t have done that to Keifer.
لذلك لا ينبغي لي أن أفعل ذلك لكيفر.
Control yourself, Jay.
السيطرة على نفسك، جاي.
Jay?
جاي؟
Yes?
نعم؟
Wow!
رائع!
Jay, the room looks so nice.
جاي، الغرفة تبدو جميلة جدًا.
Is this part of your New Year's resolution?
هل هذا جزء من قرارك للعام الجديد؟
Yes, Auntie. A new look for a new life.
نعم العمة. نظرة جديدة لحياة جديدة.
By the way, Yuri asked for permission.
بالمناسبة، طلب يوري الإذن.
He said he'll pick you up, he's probably downstairs already.
قال أنه سوف يقلك ربما يكون في الطابق السفلي بالفعل.
Ah okay, I'll go down in a while.
آه حسنًا ، سأنزل بعد قليل.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Yuri…
يوري…
Right.
يمين.
I’m already engaged, so I shouldn’t be thinking about Keifer anymore.
أنا مخطوب بالفعل، لذا لا ينبغي أن أكون كذلك أفكر في كيفر بعد الآن.
You can do this, Jay-jay.
يمكنك أن تفعل هذا، جاي جاي.
Let’s just forget what happened on New Year’s.
دعونا ننسى فقط ماذا حدث في رأس السنة.
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Give that to me, I’ll carry it.
أعطني هذا، سأحمله.
No, it’s fine. It's not heavy.
لا، لا بأس. انها ليست ثقيلة.
Why did you pick me up? I can bike on my own.
لماذا التقطتني؟ أستطيع ركوب الدراجة بمفردي.
Of course—fiancé duties.
بالطبع – واجبات الخطيب.
Fiancé…
خطيب…
Shit, it sounds so heavy.
اللعنة، يبدو ثقيلا جدا.
I’m not used to it.
أنا لست معتادًا على ذلك.
Let’s go.
دعنا نذهب.
No.
رقم
She’s not going with you.
إنها لن تذهب معك.
Leave.
يترك.
You're not the one who's going to decide here.
أنت لست الوحيد من سيقرر هنا.
Aries, it’s okay. I also want to talk to Yuri.
برج الحمل، لا بأس. أريد أيضًا التحدث إلى يوري.
If you had just listened to me,
إذا كنت قد استمعت لي للتو،
you wouldn’t have been set up in that engagement.
لن تكون كذلك أنشئت في تلك المشاركة.
Right?
يمين؟
Engagement...
خطوبة...
Set-up...
الاعداد...
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
You’ve been quiet.
لقد كنت هادئا.
Of course, I’m fine.
بالطبع أنا بخير.
Have you talked to Angelo yet?
هل تحدثت مع أنجيلو بعد؟
I'm not ready to talk to him yet.
لست مستعدًا للتحدث معه بعد.
I'm sorry, Jay.
أنا آسف، جاي.
I wasn’t honest about my feelings for you.
لم أكن صادقا بشأن مشاعري تجاهك.
But from now on, I’ll be more honest.
ولكن من الآن فصاعدا، سأكون أكثر صدقا.
We’re engaged.
نحن مخطوبون.
So I should also be honest with him about what happened on New Year’s.
لذلك يجب أن أكون صادقًا معه أيضًا حول ما حدث في رأس السنة.
Uhmm, I need to confess something—
أوممم، أريد أن أعترف بشيء —
Is it about Keifer?
هل يتعلق الأمر بكيفر؟
It's okay, Jay.
لا بأس يا جاي.
I don’t want to hear it anymore.
لا أريد أن أسمع ذلك بعد الآن.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
You don’t need to apologize.
لا تحتاج إلى الاعتذار.
I understand you,
أفهمك،
but I’ll wait for you Jay no matter how long.
لكنني سأنتظرك جاي بغض النظر عن المدة.
Even until the day of our wedding.
حتى يوم زفافنا.
If that's what it takes.
إذا كان هذا هو ما يتطلبه الأمر.
Yuri.
يوري.
I'm okay, Jay.
أنا بخير، جاي.
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
My only wish is that you give me a chance.
رغبتي الوحيدة هي ذلك أنت تعطيني فرصة.
Please don't close off your heart.
من فضلك لا تغلق قلبك.
I hope you still choose me in the end.
آمل أن تستمر في اختياري في النهاية.
Honestly,
بصراحة
I don’t even know what I feel for Yuri.
أنا لا أعرف حتى ما أشعر به تجاه يوري.
Is it guilt?
هل هو ذنب؟
Because he’s kind to me?
لأنه لطيف معي؟
Or is it because of my obligation to my family?
أم أنه بسبب واجبي تجاه عائلتي؟
Ugh, whatever. Whatever happens, happens.
اه، أيا كان. كل ما يحدث، يحدث.
Uhm...
امم...
How are we going to tell our classmates?
كيف سنفعل أخبر زملائنا؟
I don’t think they need to know.
لا أعتقد أنهم بحاجة إلى المعرفة.
Why?
لماذا؟
It’ll just cause chaos if they find out—
سوف يسبب الفوضى إذا اكتشفوا ذلك —
especially since they know Keifer has feelings for you.
خاصة وأنهم يعلمون كيفر لديه مشاعر تجاهك.
Yeah, you’re right. It might cause trouble.
نعم، أنت على حق. قد يسبب المتاعب.
Great idea.
فكرة عظيمة.
There.
هناك.
That’s good.
هذا جيد.
Ouch!
أوه!
What was that for?
لماذا كان ذلك؟
I don’t want things to be awkward between us, Jay.
لا أريد الأشياء أن يكون محرجا بيننا، جاي.
Act like the same Jay you are whenever we’re together,
تتصرف مثل نفس جاي أنت عندما نكون معًا،
and I'll do the same.
وسأفعل نفس الشيء.
You’re right.
أنت على حق.
Ouch! That really hurts!
أوه! هذا مؤلم حقا!
That’s not enough— want one on your forehead too?
هذا لا يكفي — هل تريد واحدة على جبهتك أيضًا؟
Come on, let’s go. We might be late.
هيا، لنذهب. قد نتأخر.
Wait, wait, wait.
انتظر، انتظر، انتظر.
- What? - I forgot something.
- ماذا؟ - لقد نسيت شيئا.
What?
ماذا؟
I'll go ahead.
سأمضي قدما.
Can I ask for one more favor?
هل يمكنني أن أطلب معروفًا آخر؟
What?
ماذا؟
Can you stop picking me up and taking me home?
هل يمكنك التوقف عن اصطحابي ويأخذني إلى المنزل؟
Someone might, you know, notice.
ربما شخص ما، كما تعلمون، لاحظ.
Okay.
تمام.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
Okay, Jay-jay. We'll do what is right.
حسنًا، جاي جاي. سنفعل ما هو صحيح.
You're already engaged to Yuri, time to forget about Keif—
أنت مخطوبة بالفعل ليوري، حان الوقت لنسيان أمر كيف —
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Tss. Profanity on the first day back?
خدمات الدعم التقني. الألفاظ النابية على أول يوم عودة؟
Or did you just miss my lips?
أم أنك فقط فقدت شفتي؟
What? Keifer!
ماذا؟ كيفر!
- Stop this. - Why?
- أوقف هذا. - لماذا؟
- What do you mean "why"? Keifer, please. - Stop what?
- ماذا تقصد بـ "لماذا"؟ كيفر، من فضلك. - توقف ماذا؟
This! What you're doing right now. Stop flirting with me.
هذا! ماذا تفعل الآن. توقف عن المغازلة معي.
What's wrong if I flirt with you?
ما المانع لو غازلتك؟
What's wrong if I flirt with the one I love?
ما هو الخطأ إذا كنت مغازلة مع من أحب؟
It's wrong.
هذا خطأ.
It's as if I'm cheating on Yuri.
يبدو الأمر كما لو أنني أخون يوري.
We're already engaged,
نحن مخطوبون بالفعل،
stay away from me.
ابق بعيدا عني.
Cheating?
الغش؟
We're not in a relationship.
نحن لسنا في علاقة.
So how are we cheating on him?
فكيف نخدعه؟
You're not cheating on Yuri
أنت لا تخون يوري
because we're not in a relationship.
لأننا لسنا في علاقة.
If that's the case, then leave me alone!
إذا كان هذا هو الحال، ثم اتركني وشأني!
We're not in a relationship, but…
نحن لسنا في علاقة، ولكن...
you are mine.
أنت لى.
You know what, you're crazy.
هل تعلم ماذا، أنت مجنون.
Crazy for you?
مجنون بالنسبة لك؟
Yeah, I think so.
نعم، أعتقد ذلك.
I’ll wait for you Jay no matter how long.
سأنتظرك يا جاي مهما طال الزمن.
Even until the day of our wedding.
حتى يوم زفافنا.
Fuck!
اللعنة!
You'll pay for this!
سوف تدفع ثمن هذا!
Welcome back, bro!
مرحبًا بعودتك يا أخي!
Come on, hurry, let’s play.
هيا، بسرعة، دعونا نلعب.
Jay!
جاي!
How was vacation?
كيف كانت الإجازة؟
It was okay. How about you and Mica?
كان الأمر على ما يرام. ماذا عنك وميكا؟
Obviously they ran out of condoms again—
من الواضح أنهم نفدوا الواقي الذكري مرة أخرى —
he even asked me for some. Said it wasn’t enough.
حتى أنه طلب مني بعض. قال أنه لا يكفي.
- He asked you? - Idiot!
- هو سألك؟ - غبي!
Asshole!
الأحمق!
Unbelievable!
لا يصدق!
- Ouch! - Hey, Jay!
- أوه! - مهلا، جاي!
Everyone already went on vacation but you're still sour.
لقد ذهب الجميع بالفعل في إجازة لكنك لا تزال حامضًا.
Didn't you—
أليس كذلك —
Stop it! It’s New Year, have you changed?
توقف! إنها السنة الجديدة، هل تغيرت؟
- Of course, man! - Yeah right!
- بالطبع يا رجل! - نعم صحيح!
He gambled all his Christmas money.
لقد راهن بكل أمواله في عيد الميلاد.
- Obviously. - You're really something, huh.
- بوضوح. - أنت حقا شيء، هاه.
You don't have money!
ليس لديك المال!
Hey, hey! What’s going on?
مهلا مهلا! ماذا يحدث هنا؟
How’s Grace?
كيف حال غريس؟
She has lots of cravings.
لديها الكثير من الرغبة الشديدة.
- She's always hungry. - That’s normal.
- إنها جائعة دائما. - هذا طبيعي.
Just like you.
مثلك تمامًا.
Oh really?
أوه حقًا؟
Ouch.
أوه.
- Too early in the morning. - You’re already annoying this early!
- في وقت مبكر جدا من الصباح. - أنت بالفعل مزعج في هذا الوقت المبكر!
Jay!
جاي!
Collect everyone’s contribution for the food.
جمع مساهمة الجميع للطعام.
Ignored? What’s his problem?
تجاهلت؟ ما هي مشكلته؟
Hey, where’s Ci-N?
مهلا، أين Ci-N؟
He’s not here. He’s not answering my calls.
إنه ليس هنا. إنه لا يرد على مكالماتي.
Huh? What happened to him?
هاه؟ ماذا حدث له؟
Should I go to their house later?
هل يجب أن أذهب إلى منزلهم لاحقًا؟
But what if his grumpy brother is there?
ولكن ماذا لو كان غاضبا أخي هناك؟
Hi, Jay!
مرحبًا جاي!
Damn!
اللعنة!
What happened to your lip, bro?
ماذا حدث لشفتك يا أخي؟
Did you get into a fight?
هل دخلت في قتال؟
Looks like your lips saw some action, Keif.
تشبه شفتيك رأيت بعض العمل، كيف.
You want some lip balm?
هل تريد بعض بلسم الشفاه؟
You deserve it.
أنت تستحق ذلك.
Tss.
خدمات الدعم التقني.
Hey, what's up.
مرحبا، كيف حالك.
- Rory! - Hey!
- روري! - يا!
If you look at us, it seems like nothing has changed.
إذا نظرت إلينا، يبدو أن شيئا لم يتغير.
Hey, that didn’t hit!
مهلا، هذا لم يضرب!
Throw it!
رميها!
Asshole! Hey asshole!
الأحمق! يا الأحمق!
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Chill with that.
البرد مع ذلك.
But the truth is, a lot has already changed.
ولكن الحقيقة هي، لقد تغير الكثير بالفعل.
- Hey, bro. - Ah!
- مهلا، وإخوانه. - اه!
Settle down, settle down.
يستقر، يستقر.
Welcome back, class!
مرحبًا بعودتك أيها الصف!
We’ve already started planning your retreat.
لقد بدأنا بالفعل التخطيط للتراجع الخاص بك.
We’re included in that, Sir?
ونحن مشمولون في ذلك يا سيدي؟
All students join the retreat before graduating.
جميع الطلاب ينضمون إلى التراجع قبل التخرج.
For real? So we’re actually graduating?
لريال مدريد؟ إذن نحن نتخرج بالفعل؟
All I can say is,
كل ما يمكنني قوله هو
there will be lots of activities during the retreat.
سيكون هناك الكثير من الأنشطة خلال التراجع.
When is it, Sir?
متى يا سيدي؟
No definite date yet, but earlier than the usual retreat.
لا يوجد تاريخ محدد بعد، ولكن في وقت أبكر من التراجع المعتاد.
It’s just a bit tricky because of the post-final exams.
إنه أمر صعب بعض الشيء لأنه من اختبارات ما بعد النهائية.
What’s the post-final exams?
ما هي الإمتحانات ما بعد النهائية؟
There’s a fifth exam.
هناك امتحان خامس
And that determines whether a student passes or not.
وهذا يحدد ما إذا كان ينجح الطالب أم لا .
Huh?
هاه؟
Why is there even a fifth exam?
لماذا يوجد حتى امتحان خامس؟
So if a student doesn’t pass, they won’t graduate?
لذلك إذا لم ينجح الطالب، لن يتخرجوا؟
Don’t worry Jay, I got you.
لا تقلق يا جاي، لقد حصلت عليك.
You will graduate.
سوف تتخرج.
Food, food, food!
الطعام، الطعام، الطعام!
That's all?
هذا كل شيء؟
That’s all we have left.
هذا كل ما تبقى لدينا.
You guys still haven’t pitched in for the groceries.
أنتم يا رفاق مازلتم لم تفعلوا ذلك نزلت في محلات البقالة.
- True! - You’re really something, huh!
- حقيقي! - أنت حقا شيء، هاه!
Alright, alright.
حسنًا، حسنًا.
Wow, you're quick to dodge when it's time to chip in!
واو، أنت سريع في المراوغة عندما يحين وقت المشاركة!
Do you hear anything?
هل تسمع شيئا؟
One at a time!
واحد في وقت واحد!
Fine, here.
حسنًا، هنا.
- Let's split it. - Ah!
- دعونا تقسيمها. - اه!
Plate.
طبق.
Rice.
أرز.
More.
أكثر.
Just eat it already.
فقط أكله بالفعل.
Move aside.
التحرك جانبا.
And if I don’t want to?
وإذا كنت لا أريد ذلك؟
Do you want me to tell them what we did last New Year’s Eve?
هل تريد مني أن أقول لهم ماذا فعلنا ليلة رأس السنة الماضية؟
What do you want?
ماذا تريد؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
You just look cute when you eat.
أنت فقط تبدو لطيفًا عندما تأكل.
Is it bad to watch?
هل من السيء مشاهدته؟
Yes! Go away!
نعم! يبتعد!
Bro, let's share.
اخي دعنا نشارك
All of that is yours?
كل ذلك لك؟
Is there a problem, Jay?
هل هناك مشكلة يا جاي؟
Ah nothing, he’s just teasing me.
آه لا شيء، إنه يضايقني فقط.
You sure?
أنت متأكد؟
Remember, you are mine.
تذكر أنك لي.
Jay!
جاي!
No one follow me!
لا أحد يتبعني!
No one is following you.
لا أحد يتابعك.
There, nice!
هناك، لطيف!
So refreshing!
منعش جدا!
I'm sure nobody will bother me here.
أنا متأكد من أنه لن يزعجني أحد هنا.
Let me call that brat.
اسمحوا لي أن أدعو هذا الشقي.
He won’t answer.
لن يجيب.
Ugh!
آه!
Fuck!
اللعنة!
Who’s that?
من هو الذي؟
Oh, Edrix!
أوه، إدريكس!
I thought it was someone else!
اعتقدت أنه كان شخص آخر!
What are you doing here?
ما الذي تفعله هنا؟
Sorry.
آسف.
I just couldn’t help it.
أنا فقط لا أستطيع مساعدته.
Do you have a problem?
هل لديك مشكلة؟
I’m mad at myself!
أنا غاضب من نفسي!
I'm such a coward!
أنا جبان!
Why?
لماذا؟
Unrequited love is just so damn hard!
الحب بلا مقابل هو مجرد لعنة صعبة للغاية!
I can’t even tell her…
لا أستطيع حتى أن أخبرها…
or show her.
أو تبين لها.
Yeah, that’s really hard.
نعم، هذا صعب حقًا.
But at least you’re sure.
لكن على الأقل أنت متأكد.
It’s only one person.
إنه شخص واحد فقط.
It's harder when you're stuck between two.
الأمر أصعب عندما تكون عالقًا بين اثنين.
But who is it anyway?
ولكن من هو على أي حال؟
Wow, she’s pretty!
واو، إنها جميلة!
Freya really is pretty.
فريا جميلة حقا.
Yeah, she’s really—WHAT?
نعم، إنها حقًا - ماذا؟
That's Freya?
هذه فريا؟
F-Freya is the one you’re talking about?
إف فريا هو الشخص الذي تتحدث عنه؟
Yeah.
نعم.
It's been a long time Jay.
لقد مر وقت طويل جاي.
Wow, what a revelation.
واو، يا له من الوحي.
But...
لكن...
let’s keep this between us, okay?
لنبقي هذا بيننا، حسنًا؟
Promise?
يعد؟
You don’t have food?
ليس لديك طعام؟
That’s food?
هذا طعام؟
Yeah, we were eating downstairs.
نعم، كنا نأكل في الطابق السفلي.
And you’re here being dramatic.
وأنت هنا دراماتيكي.
Whose is this?
لمن هذا؟
- Auntie, I’m really starving promise. - Looks like it.
- عمتي، أنا حقا جائعة الوعد. - يبدو ذلك.
Don’t worry, there’s another box there.
لا تقلق، هناك صندوق آخر هناك.
All of that is for you.
كل ذلك لك.
We have a visitor?
لدينا زائر؟
Relax, there’s more in the kitchen.
استرخ، هناك المزيد في المطبخ.
- This tastes so good, Auntie. - Good?
- هذا الأذواق جيدة جدا، العمة. - جيد؟
Ci-N?
سي-ن؟
You idiot!
أنت أحمق!
What happened to you?
ما حدث لك؟
Do you know how worried I was, you brat?!
هل تعرف كيف كنت قلقة، أيها الشقي؟!
Really?
حقًا؟
You were concerned about me?
هل كنت قلقة بشأني؟
Wow, you’re so sweet, Jay.
واو، أنت لطيف جدًا يا جاي.
Don’t be like that, Jay-jay!
لا تكن هكذا يا جاي جاي!
Sorry, Auntie.
آسف، العمة.
This kid didn't attend school today.
هذا الطفل لم يذهب للمدرسة اليوم
I’ll leave you two to catch up.
سأترككما للحاق بهما.
I’ll prepare dinner.
سأقوم بإعداد العشاء.
Thank you, Auntie.
شكرا لك، العمة.
You've got some nerve!
لديك بعض الأعصاب!
Enjoying the food too much, huh?
الاستمتاع بالطعام أكثر من اللازم، أليس كذلك؟
Why weren’t you in class?
لماذا لم تكن في الصف؟
It hurts, Jay!
إنه يؤلم يا جاي!
- Oh really! - I’ll tell Auntie!
- أوه حقًا! - سأخبر العمة!
What happened to you?
ما حدث لك؟
What’s the problem?
ما هي المشكلة؟
Because…
لأن…
my brother locked me up.
حبسني أخي.
He said...
قال...
he’s sending me to London because I keep on causing trouble.
لقد أرسلني إلى لندن لأنني أواصل التسبب في المشاكل.
Said I’m wasting my potential.
قال إنني أضيع إمكاناتي.
Of course I wasn’t going to allow that.
بالطبع لم أكن لأسمح بذلك.
So yeah, he locked me in my room.
لذا نعم، حبسني في غرفتي.
I was worried about you.
لقد كنت قلقة عليك.
Sorry…
آسف…
He confiscated my gadgets,
قام بمصادرة أدواتي،
I couldn’t message you.
لم أستطع مراسلتك
Is that all he did?
هل هذا كل ما فعله؟
He didn't hit you?
هو لم يضربك؟
No!
لا!
You know why?
هل تعلم لماذا؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Because I ran away.
لأنني هربت.
- Seriously? - Yeah.
- بجد؟ - نعم.
He said if I won’t listen, I should just leave.
قال إذا لم أسمع يجب أن أغادر فحسب.
Where would you go?
أين ستذهب؟
Here. With you!
هنا. معك!
That’s not allowed, are you crazy?!
هذا غير مسموح، هل أنت مجنون؟!
Why not? Angelo said it was okay.
ولم لا؟ قال أنجيلو أنه بخير.
What Angelo?
ماذا انجيلو؟
You made that up!
لقد صنعت ذلك!
Right Angelo, it’s okay?
صحيح أنجيلو، لا بأس؟
Yes, that’s true.
نعم هذا صحيح.
Oh—see?
أوه، ترى؟
That hurts!
هذا مؤلم!
My new home.
منزلي الجديد.
Won’t they look for you?
لن يبحثوا عنك؟
No, Mom knows.
لا، أمي تعرف.
I told her.
قلت لها.
Wow.
رائع.
Of all the people who left home, you're the only one who asked for permission.
من بين كل الأشخاص الذين غادروا المنزل، أنت الوحيد الذي طلب الإذن.
Amazing.
مدهش.
Of course— so Mom knows where I’m going.
بالطبع — حتى تعرف أمي إلى أين سأذهب.
Where are you even going to sleep?
أين ستنام حتى؟
Angelo said in your room.
قال أنجيلو في غرفتك.
My room?
غرفتي؟
- Do you want some? - Yeah.
- هل تريد بعض؟ - نعم.
Race you to your room!
سباق لك إلى غرفتك!
Idiot! No eating there!
غبي! لا الأكل هناك!
Hey!
يا!
Ci-N!
سي-ن!
[Ci-N singing]
[غناء Ci-N]
Good morning.
صباح الخير.
Get up! Your pillow is soaked with your drool.
استيقظ! وسادتك مبلولة بلعابك.
Ci-N, you're so noisy!
Ci-N، أنت صاخب جدًا!
So early in the morning!
في وقت مبكر جدا من الصباح!
I'll go ahead, Jay.
سأمضي قدما، جاي.
Going downstairs to eat.
الذهاب إلى الطابق السفلي لتناول الطعام.
Wow, feel at home.
واو، أشعر وكأنك في المنزل.
Ouch.
أوه.
Did Aries do something to you?
هل فعل برج الحمل شيئًا لك؟
What? What did he do?
ماذا؟ ماذا فعل؟
Let’s go.
دعنا نذهب.
Huh?
هاه؟
Ci, wait—talk to me.
Ci، انتظر – تحدث معي.
What did Aries do to you?
ماذا فعل بك برج الحمل؟
Is it true, Jay?
هل هذا صحيح يا جاي؟
You’re leaving Section E?
هل ستغادر القسم هـ؟
Did Aries tell you that?
هل أخبرك برج الحمل بذلك؟
He said I should stay away from you because you’re leaving.
وقال أنني يجب أن أبقى بعيدا منك لأنك تغادر.
No, don’t stay away from me.
لا، لا تبتعد عني.
- Crazy. - Don’t listen to him.
- مجنون. - لا تستمع إليه.
Who said that?
من قال ذلك؟
Who said you'll leave Section E?
من قال أنك ستترك القسم "هـ"؟
Who's fighting?
من يقاتل؟
Is there a cockfight?
هل هناك مصارعة الديوك؟
Jay, you’re leaving Section E?
جاي، هل ستغادر القسم هـ؟
No!
لا!
But that’s what he said!
ولكن هذا ما قاله!
Why would he say that?
لماذا يقول ذلك؟
You don’t want to be with us anymore, Jay?
أنت لا تريد أن تكون مع لنا بعد الآن، جاي؟
We can still tolerate your sour attitude.
لا يزال بإمكاننا تحمل موقفك الحامض.
I thought we were solid Section E.
اعتقدت أننا قسم قوي E.
- Ouch! - Yeah.
- أوه! - نعم.
We thought nothing could break us.
كنا نظن أن لا شيء يمكن أن يكسرنا.
- Exactly. - So dramatic!
- بالضبط. - دراماتيكية جدًا!
It’s not like that!
الأمر ليس كذلك!
Was it Aries?!
هل كان برج الحمل؟!
Keifer, stop!
كيفر، توقف!
Jay, don’t leave! Stay in Section E!
جاي، لا تغادر! البقاء في القسم E!
- Don’t leave! - Ci, enough!
- لا تغادر! - سي، بما فيه الكفاية!
- I don’t care! - Jay, please don’t!!
- لا أهتم! - جاي، من فضلك لا تفعل ذلك!!
What is happening here?!
ماذا يحدث هنا؟!
Jay-jay is leaving Section E!
جاي جاي يغادر القسم E!
- Stop! - Jay, please!
- قف! - جاي، من فضلك!
Is that true?
هل هذا صحيح؟
I’m not!
أنا لست كذلك!
Look—I’ll explain later!
انظر – سأشرح لك لاحقاً!
Go to Keifer first, he might go after Aries! Hurry!
اذهب إلى كيفر أولاً، قد يلاحق برج الحمل! عجل!
- Ci, no one's leaving! - Jay please please!
- Ci، لا أحد يغادر! - جاي من فضلك من فضلك!
I’m not leaving!
أنا لا أغادر!
- So dramatic! - Really?
- دراماتيكية جدًا! - حقًا؟
Yes! That's what I've been saying!
نعم! هذا ما كنت أقوله!
Aries told me to choose:
قال لي برج الحمل أن أختار:
Either I leave Section E,
إما أن أترك القسم هـ،
or he won't give me my Dad's number.
أو أنه لن يعطيني رقم والدي.
But I chose you guys, okay?! Happy now?!
لكنني اخترتكم يا رفاق، حسنًا؟! سعيد الآن؟!
Let's go, we need to follow Keifer!
هيا بنا، علينا أن نتبع كيفر!
Hurry!
عجل!
- Let’s go! - I don’t want to! Why?
- دعنا نذهب! - لا أريد! لماذا؟
Are you paying me for this? I don't want to!
هل تدفع لي مقابل هذا؟ لا أريد أن!
Get up!
استيقظ!
Come here.
تعال الى هنا.
Is that it, huh?!
هل هذا هو، هاه؟!
Let's go, quickly!
دعنا نذهب بسرعة!
What? Let's finish this here now!
ماذا؟ دعونا ننهي هذا هنا الآن!
Okay, let's end it here.
حسنًا، لننهي الأمر هنا.
Can someone stop them?!
هل يستطيع أحد أن يوقفهم؟!
Enough! Stop it already!
كافٍ! توقف عن ذلك بالفعل!
I guess the rumors are true, it's really a mess here.
أعتقد أن الإشاعات صحيحة إنها حقًا فوضى هنا.
Can those losers get out of here already?
هل يمكن لهؤلاء الخاسرين الخروج من هنا بالفعل؟
Especially you!
خصوصا أنت!
Enough! Don't you dare speak to Jay-jay like that!
كافٍ! لا تجرؤ على التحدث إلى جاي جاي بهذه الطريقة!
Jay-jay, you need to leave.
جاي جاي، عليك أن تغادر.
Things are getting out of control because of you.
الأمور تخرج من السيطرة بسببك.
As if.
كما لو.
Stop it already, let's go.
توقف عن ذلك بالفعل، فلنذهب.
Not until you swear!
ليس حتى أقسم!
Swear in front of Aries, you'll never leave us!
اقسم امام برج الحمل, لن تتركنا أبدًا!
Now!
الآن!
Sorry.
آسف.
I'm sorry, Aries.
أنا آسف يا برج الحمل.
I've said this before, and I'll say it again.
لقد قلت هذا من قبل، وسأقولها مرة أخرى.
I'm not leaving Section E.
لن أغادر القسم هـ.
Yes!
نعم!
Won’t karma get you for that?
لن الكرمة تحصل على ذلك؟
That's your decision.
هذا هو قرارك.
I hope you won't regret it.
آمل أنك لن تندم على ذلك.
You just lost your chance to be with your father.
لقد فقدت فرصتك للتو كن مع والدك.
So stupid!
غبي جدا!
That's what you used to blackmail Jay-jay?
هذا ما استخدمته لابتزاز جاي جاي؟
Are you forgetting who I am?
هل نسيت من أنا؟
I always get what I want.
أنا دائما أحصل على ما أريد.
Tss.
خدمات الدعم التقني.
Don't worry, Jay.
لا تقلق يا جاي.
I promise I'm gonna connect you to your father.
أعدك أنني سأفعل يوصلك إلى والدك.
How did you know I was here?
كيف عرفت أنني كنت هنا؟
Uhh, Edrix said you're hanging out here to get some air.
اه، إدريكس قال أنك تتسكع هنا للحصول على بعض الهواء.
It hasn't even been a week of classes, yet you got into a fight already.
لم يكن حتى أسبوع من الفصول الدراسية، ومع ذلك دخلت في قتال بالفعل.
My hands hurt.
يدي تؤلمني.
Do it for me.
افعل ذلك من أجلي.
Ouch!
أوه!
Be gentle!
كن لطيفا!
Who told you to get into a fight then?
ومن قال لك أن تدخل في قتال إذن؟
Always losing your temper.
دائما تفقد أعصابك.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Wow! You're getting good at apologizing, huh.
رائع! أنت تصبح جيدًا في الاعتذار، هاه.
"I'm sorry". Say it one more time.
"أنا آسف". قلها مرة أخرى.
One more, come on. One more time.
واحد آخر، هيا. مرة أخرى.
Stop making fun of me.
توقف عن السخرية مني.
I only apologize to you.
أنا فقط أعتذر لك.
Why just me?
لماذا أنا فقط؟
I'm sure you've got a long list of people you need to apologize to.
أنا متأكد من أن لديك قائمة طويلة من الأشخاص تحتاج إلى الاعتذار ل.
Who's first? Aries, and then—
من هو الأول؟ برج الحمل، وبعد ذلك —
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
I don't have feelings for any of them.
ليس لدي مشاعر تجاه أي منهم.
Only for you.
فقط لأجلك.
Whatever!
أيا كان!
Please stay.
يرجى البقاء.
Keifer…
كيفر…
I'm not giving up on you, Jay.
أنا لا أتخلى عنك، جاي.
I'll fight for you.
سأقاتل من أجلك.
What kind of dream was that?
أي نوع من الحلم كان ذلك؟
That didn't happen, but it felt so real.
ذلك لم يحدث، لكنها شعرت بأنها حقيقية جدًا.
Enough, Jay-jay!
كفى يا جاي جاي!
Good morning, Jay! See you.
صباح الخير يا جاي! أرك لاحقًا.
Ci-N?
سي-ن؟
I went ahead, Jay!
لقد تقدمت يا جاي!
You’re impossible to wake, you just kept on groaning.
من المستحيل أن تستيقظ، لقد واصلت التأوه.
Shit!
القرف!
That brat's really gonna get it from me later.
هذا الشقي سوف يحصل حقا مني لاحقا.
He actually left me?
هل تركني فعلاً؟
And even brought my bike with him!
وحتى أحضر دراجتي معه!
- What? - Looks like you're late too.
- ماذا؟ - يبدو أنك تأخرت أيضاً.
I woke up late, how about you?
لقد استيقظت متأخرا، ماذا عنك؟
I woke up late, too.
استيقظت متأخرا أيضا.
Okay, let's go.
حسنًا، دعنا نذهب.
What’s with you?
ماذا بك؟
Don’t look back.
لا تنظر إلى الوراء.
- Why? - Someone's following us.
- لماذا؟ - شخص ما يتبعنا.
Wait, don't look.
انتظر، لا تنظر.
What?
ماذا؟
Call Keifer.
اتصل بكيفر.
Huh?
هاه؟
Quickly.
بسرعة.
Wait, wait.
انتظر، انتظر.
There's the girl.
هناك الفتاة.
Jay, run!
جاي، اهرب!
Hey!
يا!
Jay-jay, I told you to leave, why are you still here?
جاي جاي، لقد طلبت منك أن تغادر، لماذا لا تزال هنا؟
Jay, leave!
جاي، غادر!
The girl!
الفتاة!
I won't leave you alone here!
لن أتركك وحدك هنا!
Go!
يذهب!
Are you okay?
هل أنت بخير؟
I'm good, are you okay?
أنا بخير، هل أنت بخير؟
What was that?!
ماذا كان هذا؟!
You thought you won already?
هل اعتقدت أنك فزت بالفعل؟
That's just a hint of what's about to come.
وهذا مجرد تلميح لما هو على وشك أن يأتي.
What do you need from us?
ماذا تحتاج منا؟
Her.
ها.
We know she's Keifer's girlfriend.
نحن نعلم أنها صديقة كيفر.
Huh?! He's not my boyfriend!
هاه؟! إنه ليس صديقي!
He said it so himself that we're not in a relationship!
لقد قال ذلك بنفسه نحن لسنا في علاقة!
Do you think we'll believe you?
هل تعتقد أننا سوف نصدقك؟
Jay, we need to escape them.
جاي، نحن بحاجة للهروب منهم.
How?
كيف؟
Just surrender Keifer's girlfriend to us so it's over with.
فقط قم بتسليم صديقة كيفر لنا لذلك انتهى الأمر.
This guy's annoying.
هذا الرجل مزعج.
Insist it all you want, I'm not his girlfriend!
أصر على ذلك كما تريد، أنا لست صديقته!
And it'll be a bigger mess if I give her to you.
وسوف تكون فوضى أكبر إذا أعطيتها لك.
Jay!
جاي!
We’ll go ahead.
سنمضي قدما.
Where are you?
أين أنت؟
Why do I feel like something is wrong?
لماذا أشعر أن هناك خطأ ما؟
Were you able to contact her?
هل تمكنت من الاتصال بها؟
You don't have to hide it from me.
ليس عليك أن تخفيه عني.
I already know.
أنا أعرف بالفعل.
I'm saying this so it's clear…
أقول هذا حتى يكون الأمر واضحًا...
I'm not backing down.
أنا لا أتراجع.
Even if we're engaged already?
حتى لو كنا مخطوبين بالفعل؟
I don't care.
لا أهتم.
Let Jay-jay decide.
دع جاي جاي يقرر.
I'll only stop when she tells me to.
سأتوقف فقط عندما تطلب مني ذلك.
Why is Jay-jay still not here?
لماذا جاي جاي لا يزال غير موجود هنا؟
Do you know where she is?
هل تعرف أين هي؟
No.
رقم
Keifer!
كيفر!
The tracker shows Jay-jay is in the hospital.
يُظهر المتعقب جاي جاي هو في المستشفى.
What?!
ماذا؟!
Drix, go!
دريكس، اذهب!
Boys, over here!
الأولاد، هنا!
Where are you Jay?
أين أنت جاي؟
I'm going crazy.
انا مجنون.
Miss, is there a Jasper Jean Mariano here?
يا آنسة، هل هناك جاسبر؟ جان ماريانو هنا؟
Wait Sir, I'll check.
انتظر يا سيدي، سوف أتحقق.
Faster, Miss!
أسرع يا آنسة!
I don't have time!
ليس لدي الوقت!
Sir, there's no Jasper Jean Mariano admitted here.
سيدي، ليس هناك جاسبر اعترف جان ماريانو هنا.
- Huh? - What time was she admitted?
- هاه؟ - في أي وقت تم قبولها؟
A while ago, check it again! Faster!
منذ فترة، التحقق من ذلك مرة أخرى! أسرع!
Sorry Sir, but there's—
آسف يا سيدي، ولكن هناك —
Miss, check it again please.
سيدتي، تحققي من ذلك مرة أخرى من فضلك.
Guys, here!
يا شباب، هنا!
Jay!
جاي!
Jay, I’m coming.
جاي، أنا قادم.
Good thing the wound isn't that deep.
من الجيد أن الجرح ليس بهذا العمق
You shouldn't be lifting heavy things for one week.
لا ينبغي عليك أن ترفع أشياء ثقيلة لمدة أسبوع واحد.
Where's Jay-jay?
أين جاي جاي؟
She was right there a while ago.
لقد كانت هناك منذ فترة.
She disappeared all of a sudden, she was probably shocked by all the blood.
واختفت فجأة، ربما صدمت من كل الدماء.
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
I don't know, bro.
لا أعرف يا أخي.
She just started shaking when she saw me bleeding.
لقد بدأت للتو في الاهتزاز عندما رأتني أنزف.
She didn't talk...
لم تتكلم...
she just kept on crying.
لقد استمرت في البكاء.
Fuck.
اللعنة.
Ever since Ram's gang weakened,
منذ أن ضعفت عصابة رام،
everyone popped out of nowhere.
الجميع برزت من العدم.
And they all want to get Jay-jay
وجميعهم يريدون الحصول على جاي جاي
because she's Keifer's girlfriend.
لأنها صديقة كيفر.
I don't even know.
أنا لا أعرف حتى.
I'm just grateful that David came to help us.
أنا فقط ممتن لذلك لقد جاء ديفيد لمساعدتنا.
If it wasn't for him, we wouldn't even reach the hospital.
لو لم يكن من أجله، لن نصل حتى إلى المستشفى.
Rory, your coffee.
روري، قهوتك.
Next time, call me.
في المرة القادمة، اتصل بي.
Don't try to be a fucking hero.
لا تحاول أن تكون بطلا سخيف.
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
How is she?
كيف حالها؟
She looked terrified when I found them.
بدت مرعوبة عندما وجدتهم.
With all that blood, I thought it was her who got stabbed.
بكل تلك الدماء اعتقدت أنها هي التي طعنت.
But she was just hugging Rory.
لكنها كانت تعانق روري فقط.
Why did this happen?
لماذا حدث هذا؟
What stupid shit did Keifer do this time for Jay-jay to get involved again?
ما هو القرف الغبي الذي فعله كيفر هذه المرة لكي يتدخل جاي جاي مرة أخرى؟
They all want to use Jay-jay to beat Keifer.
انهم جميعا يريدون استخدامها جاي جاي يهزم كيفر.
Huh?
هاه؟
Keifer never uses his head!
كيفر لا يستخدم رأسه أبدا!
So, what's your plan?
إذن، ما هي خطتك؟
None yet.
لا شيء حتى الآن.
But when I get back, they better prepare themselves.
لكن عندما أعود، من الأفضل أن يعدوا أنفسهم.
Why?
لماذا؟
Why didn't I black out?
لماذا لم أفقد الوعي؟
Why didn't I attack them like how I did to Cyrus and Ram?
لماذا لم أهاجمهم مثلما فعلت مع سايروس ورام؟
A lot has happened ever since I wore this uniform.
لقد حدث الكثير منذ ذلك الحين ارتديت هذا الزي الرسمي.
Stop it!
توقف!
But among all of them, this one's the worst.
لكن من بين كل هؤلاء، هذا هو الأسوأ.
Jay!
جاي!
Keifer…
كيفر…
No, no.
لا، لا.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
I'm here, don't cry.
أنا هنا، لا تبكي.
Please don't cry, I'm here.
من فضلك لا تبكي، أنا هنا.
Don't cry, it's okay.
لا تبكي، لا بأس.
I'm here.
أنا هنا.
Don't cry.
لا تبكي.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Is this your blood?
هل هذا دمك؟
Are you hurt?
هل تأذيت؟
No.
رقم
I thought the same incident with Ram would happen again.
اعتقدت نفس الحادث مع رام سيحدث مرة أخرى.
I was scared.
كنت خائفة.
It's okay, everything's okay.
لا بأس، كل شيء على ما يرام.
Everything’s okay.
كل شيء على ما يرام.
Stop crying.
توقف عن البكاء.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
I saw lots of blood
رأيت الكثير من الدماء
but I didn't faint nor harm anyone.
لكنني لم أغمي عليه ولم أؤذي أحدا.
And we'll figure out why.
وسنكتشف السبب.
But for now, let's get you cleaned up.
لكن في الوقت الحالي، دعنا ننظفك
I know this is wrong because Yuri's my fiancé already.
أعلم أن هذا خطأ لأنه يوري هو خطيبي بالفعل.
But why do I feel this way?
لكن لماذا أشعر بهذه الطريقة؟
When it comes to Keifer,
عندما يتعلق الأمر بكيفر،
my feelings are certain.
مشاعري مؤكدة.
Wait, what are you going to do?
انتظر، ماذا ستفعل؟
You need rest.
أنت بحاجة إلى الراحة.
Just shut up and let me.
فقط اصمت واسمحوا لي.
I'm not giving up on you, Jay.
أنا لا أتخلى عنك، جاي.
I'll fight for you.
سأقاتل من أجلك.
Is this still a dream?
هل ما زال هذا حلما؟
Shit, someone wake me up!
اللعنة، شخص ما أيقظني!
Game on.
تشغيل اللعبة.
Don’t just let them take what’s yours.
لا تدعهم يأخذون ما هو لك فقط.
Just because they dared to make a bold move.
فقط لأنهم تجرأوا للقيام بخطوة جريئة.
Follow your heart.
اتبع قلبك.
Don't listen to distractions and don't give them an inch.
لا تستمع إلى الانحرافات ولا تعطوهم شبرًا.
Were you the one who taught them?
هل أنت من علمتهم؟
Out of all the boys in Section E, five of us can do Martial Arts.
من بين جميع الأولاد في القسم هـ، خمسة منا يمكنهم ممارسة الفنون القتالية.
Six if you include Mayo too.
ستة إذا قمت بتضمين المايونيز أيضًا.
Oh "kapour"!
يا "كابور"!
- "Kapour!" - Parkour!
- "كابور!" - باركور!
You said "kapour"!
لقد قلت "كابور"!
Stupid, it's parkour!
غبي، إنه الباركور!
If I'm the stupid one, then what are you?
إذا أنا الشخص الغبي، ثم ما أنت؟
Attention-seeker!
طالب الاهتمام!
Asshole!
الأحمق!
Profanity.
الألفاظ النابية.
I'm jealous.
أنا غيور.
I can't help it, Jay.
لا أستطيع مساعدته، جاي.
You agreed to be my fiancée.
لقد وافقت على أن تكون خطيبتي.
Fuck, it's because of Jay-jay?!
اللعنة، إنه بسبب جاي جاي؟!
Wait, no!
انتظر، لا!
It isn't what it looks like!
إنه ليس كما يبدو!
Kit!
عدة!
Even blaming Kit!
حتى إلقاء اللوم على كيت!
Stop talking to Jay-jay like that!
توقف عن التحدث إلى جاي جاي بهذه الطريقة!
Go flirt with everybody in Section E!
اذهب لمغازلة الجميع في القسم E!
You're no different from Ella, anyway!
أنت لا تختلف عن إيلا، على أية حال!